谨以此片追忆逝去的童年，如果你也有这样的童年的话欢迎加入我们的贴吧"神剑传奇"。本作品之片源来自互联网，版权归原公司所有。任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途，一切后果由该组织或个人承担！制作者不承担任何法律及连带责任！请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
作司
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
F
FRance 2, Ecipse Animatic
2.∈psc
n productionsⅫ l Ins
F
2.∈
France 2, Ecipse Animat ion, Tooncan PRoducr ions Xll Ine.
F
2.∈ clips An
An
FRance 2. Ecipse Animaz ion, Tooncan PRoductions Xll Ine
校对：
2.∈
pc oy
ChRistophe pujol and Amelie AubeRt
BCRIPT nu
Christophe potok ard Amelie Aurene
Look how brightly my mother's
star is shining tonight, Wip
威普看我母后那颗星星今晚闪得多亮啊
You're right, Princess.
没错公主殿下
But I,m not surprised
可我一点也不奇怪
It's especially
bright from this spot
从这个地方观看尤其亮
Come see!
跟我来看啊
This is the very place
这里就是
that your parents
met for the first time
你父母第一次遇见的地方
was there
我当时也在
Filthy little snoops.
丑陋的小闲事公
s for saphire
s代表索非亚
E for Erwann
而E代表伊万
I envy you, Wip
我真羡慕你威普
I don,'t have any memories
of my parents together.
我没有一点我父王和母后在一起的记忆
I was too young.
那时候我太小了
Djana! Watch out!
裘娜小心
Walka!
是沃卡
Balls of fire: fly
火球去
第？集
A
Tara
塔拉
Fly
去
八
Nice shot, Herik!
好准头哈里克
You're finally
getting the hang of it
你终于完全掌握了
F
Are you alright?
你没事吧
can't move my leg
我的腿动不了
Iceal'trmoweemmyylega
毛论的围运麻不不了
cant move my ag
我的腿动不了
ther than that I'm fine!
其他地方没事
The dart just grazed you
她的羽毛把你的腿擦伤了
a bit of shogi medicine
and you'll be as good as new
只要上点三基寺的药马上就完好如新
One day I'll get you, Djana!
总有一天我会找你算账的裘娜
Do you hear me?
听到没有
I will destroy your life
as you have destroyed mine
你破坏了我的生活我也不会让你好过的
我破坏了你的生活吗
No. Walka
you chose your own path
不沃卡是你自己选择了那条路
Alkal
What has happened to you?
卡你怎么
It's Kwwodhan's swonk dsmit- ut
是划派平的唱吧
Iss kwoxdarr's waiko Csn't it
是您平的观
It's weodhan's work, isn!t
是然的好事对
Answer me. Walka
回答我沃卡
My sylph bracelet! No
我的精灵手镯你不能这样
You Cewe chosen to be evil
s0-fll-make you look the part
你择了邪恶一方所以我会让
尔看起来也符合邪恶的形象
要
N
Ahl Nol
啊不要
N
Ah! NOl
AhI N
啊不要
Ahl No
NOI
不要
N
要
NO!
不要
I just don't understand it.
我就是不明白
It was Walka who turned her
back on Fedora and my mother
是她自己背叛了费德拉和我母后
but she blames me for her misery
可她却把自己的不幸归咎到我头上
Why does my
own Aunt hate me so?
为什么我自己的姨妈这么恨我
Don' t let it trouble you, princess
别为这烦恼了公主殿下
No one can tell
what happened to Walka,
除了当时在场的人
unless they were there
谁也不知道沃卡经历了什么事
Wip, you are absolutely right.
威普你说得很对
Djana? Where are you going?
裘娜你去哪啊
Tara can't ride
拉现在骑不了马
I'm going to brocelianda
我去波西里安达
Catch up with me when you, can
你们尽快赶过来吧
I can't leave Tara alone
and vulnerable all, night
我不能让塔拉单独呆整个晚
那样很容易再受伤
Can' t this wait till morning
就不能等到明天早上吗
I hate it when she gets that look
我真讨厌看到她那个表情
F
Well. well
m good friends the Imps!
是我的朋友捣蛋鬼们
知
要
Ask them to helpus
get into the Water Palace
g
让他们帮我进入水
飞
二
是
多
篇
了
Fedora?
费
He says Fedora
still hasnt recovered
他说自从上次为了保护森林受彷后
会半样这Y目细
peanooeluseu-Ins
elope SAES PH
He says Fedora
still hasn't recovered
他说自从上次为了保森林受伤后
from her last defence of the forest
费德拉尚未恢复过来
Then she can't tell me anything
么她不能告诉我什
or send me back to the past
也不能把我送回过去
Xcalibur
on your power.
神剑请我量吧
Djana. have you dost-your mind?
装娜你是不疯
That's much too dangerous!
敌大危险了
want to know
why Walka hates me
我想知道为什么讨厌我
Maybe I can make things right
也许我可以让事情转变过来
Xcalibur Sword of Justice
help me to know the truth
神剑正义之剑请帮我了解事实真相
Take me to he past.
热遐间测去咽
Take me⑩e化
贱我送圆过去吧
Take me to the past
把我送回过去吧
Princess
公主殿下
Aren, t you curious, Wip?
你不好奇吗威普
I can,' t believe I'm doing this
难以相信我正这么做
Boy! Habor!
Are we beii
reborn!
天啊我仙是不是太顽固了唧
The water palace!
是水
Look, Wip! Fedora isn't here
威普看费德拉不在这里
We're in the past
我们回到过去了
Wel川be!
真见鬼
That's…that'sme!
那那是我
That'soao that's mel
D
m
What will happen if I see myself?
看到了另一介自己会发生什么事呢
What if two Wips
cancel each other out
要是个威普让易一个威普消失怎么办
I am- delighted that you
have fallen in, love, Walka
沃卡你找到了真爱真替你高兴
but at the same time I shall
be very sorry to lose a sister
可同时我也恨遗憾要失去一个姐妹
You know tha
you marry a human
要知道如果你
人类
you will haye /to leave the
orest of Brocelianda foreve
你就得永远离开波西里安达
I know , Fedora:
我知道费德拉
Believe me t won't
be easy to leave
home
相信我离开自己家也不件容易的事
Walka? Has a date with a prince?
沃卡跟某位亲王约会吗
I think she'd
better have a chaperone
我想她最好找个女伴一起
A
I'm not sure can ride
我不确定能不能骑
How long does your, Shogi
medicine take to work, anyway?
你这三基寺药要多久才能见效啊
It will work a lot faster
if you stay off /that leg
如果不动那条腿很快就会见效
It's light now
在天亮了
Will you be all right
如果我去找裘娜让你留在这里
eave you here
and go after Diana alone?
吗
I'llemanage
我能
A
产
Djana? Djana. where are you?
裘娜裘娜你在哪
Diana?
裘娜
Are you here
你在这吗
Djana
裘娜
Fedora
费德拉
A
e
Fedora, need your help
I am looking for Djana
费德拉我需你的帮助我在找费明
Djana has gone back/in time
裘娜回到过
and I fear she will
do something reckless
我担心她会不顾一切芸做些体么
You must fetch her back. herik
里克你得把她带回来
and make sure not to
change anything
并确保不改变过亲的
Take my ward.
拿着我的法村
have enough power to keep
you in th
inight falls
我的法痂的你采到日落
have enough power to keep
U have enough power to keep
you in the past until night falls
我的法为只足够社你呆到日落
Prince Erwann!
伊万亲王
I am: honoured by
your kind invitation
对于你善意的邀请我感到非常荣幸
e Sylphs have so few
occasions to leave Brocelianda
我们精灵极少有机会离开波西里安达
The honour isimine, Walka
能邀请到如些美丽的精灵光临本堡
to have someone so
beautiful grace my humble-home
这是我的荣幸沃卡
Father
父王
Who's there?
谁在那
Show yourself and
explain this intrusion!
赶紧现身说出你善闯本堡的原因
… simply want to put my
sword at your service, my lord
亲王殿下我只是前来投靠您的
Who is this girl?
这个女孩是谁
was afraid your
guards would chase me away.
我担心你的卫兵会赶我走就自己进来了
I only wish to offer
my sword services, my lord
我只是想来投靠您亲王殿下
Well well, you
certainly are bold
你还真大
Guard!
卫兵
Those eyes
那双眼睛
They are exactly like Sapphire
和索非亚的眼睛太象了
Take this young
lady to the captain.
带这位女士去见队长
So that he can
evaluate
combat skill
让队长诞估下她的战斗能力
thank you, kind sir
非常感谢您给我这个机会殿下
A
吧
Now where were we?
现在我们进行到哪了啊
Djana? Djana
裘娜你在吗
Where can she be?
她能去哪啊
A已wams
在伊的哩吗
Af. Erwaruru's Castle?
在伊的城堡里吗
E
学
Terrific shot!
不起的箭法
What a remarkable young girl
多奇特的一位女孩啊
he girl is an
intruder from the future
这个女孩是来自未来的擅闯者
apphire and Erwann?
亚和伊万的女
al- never accept tha
我绝对不接
的事
1o! quL-nmever acd
不还的
No! \mI never accept that
不我绝对不接受那样的事
That girl is amazing
那介女孩真让人惊讶
hgi百 5. Breakin
wonder where she's from
我想她是来自哪里呢
From somewhere
unexpected, no dout
毫无疑问她是来自意想不到的地方
What are you doing here?
你在这吗啊
Wip?
威普是你啊
Well, I'Ilb
a man
real man!
我会成为男人一个真正的男人
You know my name?
你知道我的名字啊
That's hardly fair
when donit know yours
阝可不公平我都不知道你叫什么
My name? Uh-HTerik
我的名字吗恩我是哈里克
was um.practising teleportation
恩我刚才在练习传心术
and I ended up here by mistake
不小心来错到这里
Ive heard you Shogis
spit fire like us dragons
听说你们法师能象我们龙这样喷火
s
我见识下
Can I see?
让我见识下吗
No-No! No time! Sorry.
现在没有时间抱歉
l have to c
back to the monastery
我回寺院
or my master
vill be furious. Bye
不然大法师会发怒的再见
家
Aaw, Just when
meet someone really grea
见到了真正厉害的人可
没能见识到他的真本事
You are both an excellent
rider and a remarkable. miss
小姐你是位优秀的骑手
同时也是位非凡的射手
Now let us see what
your swordsmanship=is-like
现在让我们瞧瞧你剑术如何吧
Can we do this a bit later?
我们能晚点再进行这个吗
A true knight muste be
ready for a fight at any-time
真正的骑士得随时准备迎战
on guard!
On guard
注意了
Xcalibur
神剑
You stole the Sword of
Justice from King Edwyn
你从艾德温国王那偷来了正义之剑
Herik
哈里克
Wip? What are you
and Diana doing here
威普你和裘娜来这干吗
This is crazy!
太疯狂了
He
It wasn't my idea
又不是我的主意
Where are my manners?
我的绅士风度哪里去了
May I offer you a
refreshing drink, Walka
能让我帮你拿杯清爽的饮料吗沃卡
Please allow me, my dear Erwann
请让我去吧亲爱的伊万
What was that she
put in his drink, poison?
她在饮料里面放什么了毒药吗
Don'tworry
Walka has a crush on Erwann
别担心沃卡对伊万动心了
Can you believe that?
你相信吗
Walka in love with Erwann?
你是说沃卡爱上伊万了吗
Then at some point she must
have become jealous of Sapphire
那从某个方面来说她肯定很嫉妒索非亚
No wonder she hates djana
难怪她会恨裘娜
Speaking of which, where is Djana?
说到这裘娜在哪啊
My lord, this girl is a thief!
主人这女孩是小偷
She stole xcalibur
She must be taken to the King
她偷了神剑得把她押去见国王陛下
Erwann. no!
伊万不要
(
a thief? Nonsense
That will be all, captain
小偷胡说没你的事了队长
You must forgive my captain
请别跟我的队长计较
The poor man
too blind to see that
那可怜的家伙肯定是瞎眼
someone so
charming, so beautifu
如此迷人如此美丽的女
cannot possibly be a thief
怎么可能会是小偷
Prince Erwann
伊万亲王
if this girl was caught stealing,
如果这女孩真偷了东
perhaps you should
也许你应该
Question her?
An excellent idea
审问她吗好主意
for your visit, Walka
多谢你的造访沃卡
You must come again
欢迎你再来
Alone'at last
终于可以单独相处了
And now you must
pardon my boldness
请原谅我的冒犯
don,- even know your name
我甚至都不知道你的名
but know I
will never be content
不过我知道直到你成为我的妻子
until you become my wife
我才会满足
need… some time
我需要点时间考虑一下
This is a bit sudden
这太突然了
Perhaps we could continue
this conversation this evening
也许我们可以今天晚再继续这个话题
The forest? How interesting
在树林见吗真有意思
I was looking forward to a
walk in the forest this evening
我老早就期待今晚去树林散散步
What an intriguing girl you are
你真是位有魅力的女孩
L
e
Herik! It's horrible
哈里克太恐怖了
My own father is in love with me
我父王居然爱上我了
No Djana, He's under a spell
裘娜他是中了魔
Walka gave him a love potion
沃卡给他喝了爱情迷幻药
and you just
arrived at a bad time
而你正好不合时机地出现了
A love potion?
爱情迷幻药吗
But why?
可为什么会这样
why
这样
couldn' t have made
her feel that threatened
我没让她感觉受威胁了啊
Unless ter Sylph powers.-told
Erwann's daught
除非她的精灵法力告诉了
我是伊万的女儿
she didn' t know that
如果她不知道我的身份
she would never use
her charms on him like this!
她就绝对不会用这样的方式施展财
Now my father will
never love my mother.
现在我父王不会爱上我母后
all because of me!
都是因为我
What is going on?
发生什么
There must-be an
antidote to Walka's potion
定有解药可以破解沃卡的迷幻药
No matter what Walka concocted
不管沃卡怎么捏造事实
Erwann and Sapphire will always
love each other quite naturally
伊万和索非亚自然还是会相爱的
If we can just get them togethe
如果我能让他们见到对方就好
Erwann promised to meet
me in the clearing tonight!
可况伊万答应今晚来树林见我
true love will do the rest!
真爱就会解决余下的问题
Except that Erwann
is expecting to meet you!
除非伊万正期待着见你
know that love
>makes people blind
我知道爱情可以让人盲目
but blind enough to confuse
two totally different people?
可是会盲目到分辨不出
两个完全不同的人吗
ip! You were there
减普他们第一次在树林遇见的时
when they first met
in the clearing, right?
你也在场对吧
and convince- my father
想办法让我父王相信
that-Sapphire and
I are the same person!
索非亚和我就是同一个人
What?
什么
ileuM
What?
nat
Didn't you say that
love makes people blind?
你不是说爱情会让人盲目吗
But what about the other me?
可另外一个威普怎么办啊
If two Wips show up
要是两个威普同时出现
your father will think it's a trick
你父王会认为这是个阴谋
He"might even, suspect
he's being lured into a trap
甚至可能怀疑他会被诱入圈套
No problem
没问题
know how to
eep that Wip occupied
我知道怎么让另一个威普分身无
just take me to him
你就只管带我去找他吧
Me? How
should
know where I am?
我带你去找他那我怎么知道他在哪u
Come on, Wip
回想不威普
What would you have
been doing
this time of day
7年前今天的这个时候
seventeen years ago?
你在做什么啊
一
差
don't remember
being so ridiculous!
我司不记得曾经有这么可笑
N
I just said
have to meet Sapphire
我刚才说我得去见索非亚
Hey! What's: your hurry??
嘿你们在忙什么啊
You again,apprentice Shogi?
实习法师又是你啊
Yes. I've thought about it
是我我想过了
and rea
can't pas
up a chance
不能错过机会跟如此著名的龙试
to test myself against
such a famous dragon
便测试一下我的实力到底如何
Famous? Really
我很出名真的吗
even have some
delicious prizes for the winner.
我还为获胜者准备了美味奖品哦
Youre on! Follow me!
know a quiet little spot
你说了算跟我来我知道一个安静的地方
I'm warning you though
I haven t got much time
我可先警告你我没有多少时间奉陪哦
I have to get back to my mistress
晚点我得回去找我家女主
分
We've got to hurry
my father will be there soon
我们得快点我父王很快就到了
Good <timing, Wip
晚上好啊威普
I'm looking for your mistress
我在找你家女主
Uh
haven 't seen her
呃我没有见到她
Come, come, Wip.
好了威普
Will a bit
honey help your memory?
是不是来点蜂蜜可以有助于你记忆呢
I think it's time
you talked to me, Walka!
我想是时候我们好好谈谈了沃卡
Well, well
my niece from the future
不错我来自未来的侄女
I-am Djana, daughter
f Erwann and Sapphire
我是裘娜伊和索非亚的女儿
m off. l've got an
appointment to keep
我走了还要去赴约会呢
came hoping
hat you would accept
电我来是希望你接受事实
Accept what?
接受什么事实
That, Sapphire stole
the love of my life?
索非亚偷走了我的爱人这个事实吗
My mother didn't steal anything
我母后没有偷任何东西
It was love that
brought my parents together.
是爱情让我父王母后走到一起的
What do you know about longing?
你又知道么是渴望吗
I know what it's like to
long for the love/ of my aunt
我知道就象我长久以来
渴望得到阿姨的爱一样
came here hoping
ake things right
我来这就是希望让事情有转机出现
Your father
now in love with you
你父亲现在爱
He will reject your mother
and you will never be born
他会拒绝你母亲然后你也不可能会出生
Walka. no! Don't do this
沃卡不要你不能这么
Wip! You frightened me
威普你吓到我了
I was wondering where you were
我刚还在想你去哪了呢
I'm sorry, my pri
抱歉
uh, pretty stars, aren't they
漂亮的星星对
What a lovely smell of moss!
苔藓的味道真好闻
3?
@
Did you hear that?
Someone's coming
你听到了吗有人过来了
What? Who? How? Already?
什么会是谁啊怎么过来的到了吗
I mean, don t worry, Saphire
我是说不要担心索非亚
/Walka? Let's hope
she doesn't -ruin everything
沃卡你在哪但愿她没有破坏任何事情
先
I'm sure I heard something
我确定听到什么声音了
Who could be wandering
the forest at this hour?
这个时候还会有谁在树林里散步啊
Oh! Who is that?
啊那是谁
Now don't move
I'll go see what he wants
现在不要动我去看看他想干什么
Prince Erwann!
We've been waiting for you
伊万亲王我们正等你呢
That is, my mistress and I
我家女主人和我
Good heavens, a talking dragon!
天啊一条会说话的龙
I know it might
seem strange to you
我知道听起来可能很奇怪
but my mistress has changed
a bit since this mornin
今天早上过后我家女主人有了点变化
But that's the
way it is with Sylphs
不过精灵就是那样的
ove does that to them
爱情让她们发生了变化
She is a Sylph too, like Walka?
和沃卡一样她也是精灵吗
:And did you say love?
刚才你说的是爱情吗
Of course!
But be careful what you say
当然不过请注意措辞
Hmm . Not bad
恩还不赖
But what do you think of this?
不过你看看这个怎样
Impressive! Wow! A dragon
让人印象深刻哇是条龙
奔
长
W还
e
Well
呸丕好
Nightfall! I sure hope
you,'ve done it, Dja
ana!
天黑了希望你已经完成了裘妍
You're forcing me
to pull out all the stop
你让我不得不使出全身解数
Make way for the
piece de resistance
让开点
Balls of fire. Fly
火球去
This ring only
highlights your beauty
这个戒指衬托了你的美丽
You know after all this time
don't even know your name
这半天以来我还不知道你的芳名呢
Now you're teasing me, Sapphire
现在你逗我笑了索非亚
But I think I
could put up with it
不过我想我会在往后的日子
for the rest of my life
来享受这个
多
Love can be
unexpected, Sapphire
爱情是不可求的索非亚
but you have to seize it
when you have the chance
可机会来了你就要抓住它
Listen to your heart
听你心底的呼唤吧
Walka.There they are
是沃卡他们在那
Oh, Walka!
噢沃卡
That's it
就是那样
Let's hope everything
turned out for the best
希望一切都以最好的姿态出现
Wow! Okay, you win
哇好你赢了
威普
Oh, boy, this is a better work
天啊效果太好了吧
y
Diana? Herik
裘娜哈里克是你们吗
Would somebody mind
telling me what's going on?
有人介意告诉我到底发生什么事了吗
Hooray! True love
conquered all! We did it
太棒了真爱战胜了一切我们成功了
You did it! What a dragon
你做到了了不起的龙啊
Did what?
威普做什么了啊
It's a long story, Tara
说来话长塔拉
But found out
something about Walka
不过我了解到一些沃卡的事了
She's been terribly . wounded
她被伤得很严
Wounded? Good
她受伤了吗那敢情好啊
I hope it hurts as
bad as the one she gave me
我还希望她伤得有我这么严重
It's a wound you can't see
是一种看不见的伤害
and don't know
if it will ever heal
我都不知道那种伤害是不是可以抚平
You should get
back to Brocelianda
你应该去趟波西里安达
give Fedora back her wand
把她的法杖送回去
just want to lool
at my mother's star
我就想看看我母后所在的星星
SCIPT SUPEKTISOK
EIECUTTYE STORY: EDITOR
sc HeLs rexton
execuTe ST
强
EDITOR
5CHL8HBHF°
erecuTIYE STORY EDITOR
sCRIPT suPEKYTSOR
exEcuTIVE
&TOR DITOR
5江HLBH
KECUTIYE STORY CDITON
LHYLTNSNOOL1235
rna工
EXECUT
523配Ts
STORYBOARD AKTISTS
STUDIO
LIP
STUDIO MANTGEK-. ELLrsE
PRODUCTION XDMITSTRTTOR- TOONCAH PRODUCTIONS IM INC.
PRODUCTION IOMINISTKAT
D MODELING
SRIBOUILLE
3D-MODELING
GRIBOUILLe
GKlBouILLe
reCTOR
OTOSKAPHT
PiErre MEtoN
PRODUCTION ASSISTANT
GT瓦RF
SurgKYISORS
DInn SecReT
OsRAPHY
露耀智
器器
RE0
3D题O
SuPERTISORS
器
奸式
CE IRTI
soFT
EYELOPER
C6 ARTISTE
MODELIN
翻熟袋
MOTION CAPTURE
MOTION
TuRE
sUco
MOTION CXPTURE
SIUCON STH
SIUCON STuDIO
oUteR
surekrIsoK
c∈cGNc
CECG INC
HETHTLie 1oNgermte
CGCG INC
execuT FRI9DUCER
Perso
CGCG INC
PeKYISOZ
tH SHI
AD exo
r。e素
xou真|N5 isOr
LA1.ouT a JesseN SurRnsoR
LAY-ouT a
ON SUPERTISOI
NETWORT KD
Lx。ou∝ SuPERTIsOI
TwORT KD.∈T°N
ETwORr AD陋N5TRTo
Lxy-oUT∝频
recTos段
NETWORL D
NeTwoRL TOMCTXATOR
DCISTRKTOR
是5 SuPErVIsor
NETWORL KD
LHT在SP
石s5∈o
a seaTeS TTTs supers
H在
°瓶8紫o
deNTine a suTes TsTs sureknsoR
TERS Tsi s suPeRvIsor
LIHTING C SP
SuPEkYtso
I ODEN
H
nicTure eNtEr
TOONCAN PRODUCTIONS XII
TOONCKN PRODUCTIONS XII
POSTP
舒
DITIN
POSTaP
PERTISOR
rost-bs0euCE Bo sur wt
soum°s点pm
souto nERS
RETr
ITTEE
LoTTa aote
R
QuRLTY CONT
CREDIT
QuKLTY co
PTT民
QuAUTy CoN
QUTLT) CONT
EDIT
-TORS
QuALITy CONT
CREDIT
QuALITY
CREDITS
TECHMICAL DIRECTORS
HATORS
TECl
TeCHNIC
OORDINXTORS
TeCHI
XDIMATORS
TUNKIIDTDI
SSISTANT
&Oe rOsetTe
PRODUCTION ISSUSTAHT
TEO
Pugno geTO
PRODUCTIOM ICCOUNTTHTS
PRODUCTION ISSISTANT
MTANTS
SISTINT
BeLue Dust
a江e" a
PRODUC
UNTANTS
使
x CXNKDX-FRKNCE CO PRODuCTION
开8
u女吗
ueb
Le centhe mio n beut onrt
制作
Quebec=孙光辉
匹
制作
Quebec=孙光辉
吴乐声
Canada编辑
黄金波
PRODUCED IN
PRODUCED IN KSsocImoI
Y
赉任编辑
责任编辑
邓锦绣
吴丽
IRTISTIC DIRECT
ARTISTIC DIRECT
吧
avitene pe learn et neotame N
x累TsTc
顾向
STer De t吧F
e eoea. Paste 2. caee
顾问
用品m栋华
顾向
贴 eH De TefLOn et d ury=m梁栋华c
梁栋华
2002・F2.en
监制
ELLiPSANIME
出品人
张新华
Food
孙旭阳
PRODUCT
bond
广东蓝筒英语传有限公司
Y
不到
评信备下
刘名
到传备
例情备
店各
如情备
Go onl Movel
everyone in the square!
they'll soon b
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
疗传备
对备
到
and no harm will come to you!
校对：
inoX o1 euo lM LuCey ou pue
and no harm will come to
6uyAuaAa eye pino oA
You would take everything?
entire village starve
The stror
The strong
surve
of nature, tavern keeper,
the People of the Sea
What gives
你这企
评有备
What gives you
备
nubiA
What gives
What gives you
rightI
评备
Ths OwLan
This gives me the right
刘各
Understood?
刘情舒
评到行
店方
(备
That's betterl
到一
almost too much to carr
不信
almost too much to carry
Goodl Make. the village
不
bother of coming back
评
bothered coming at a
runt, and his bodyguards
men will be lea
first for frightening these people
N‖
)
分
●
分,
C
NE
交际英语
即将播出
Nx交际英语
x交际英语特播
交际英语即将播出
NEx交际英语播
交际英语
即将播出
Nx交际英语
NEx交际英语。一算特
交际英语
即将播出
NE交际英语聊将起
NE交际英语
交际英语
即将播出
NEN交际英语一聊
交际英语
即将播出
交际英语右
交际英语
即将播出
NEx交际英语
。
、
了本飞
N
F
e0
A
基
s
水
入
4公
之
人
彭蒙惠
bidEts
空中劳室
空中英插弦室
m空中套
空中美室
器的中正
金
空申美M室
空中劳
S1OVOMnIn
stove Marth
TiMoti
fttrThishirAiDHLl
Enler knushnnkyLmmngr
山 Rachellsawntzk
Esther krushniakynng
haWeIS
VEIMEOb CHID EwAld
Chelsoalewalda
山 cheW
CholsohEwald
山 Chip Ewa
Chelsea Ewald
nil DorIs Brougham
KOnIng
u叫 oJ8I9NOG CH
Hemo Dorls Brougham
KomiTee
EIMER DoUS Brougham
KendLe
Ea山 Dovis Brough
KoniGe
ogham
SeniLe
ghat
二g
g“址
lInda ludwig
H'lMERb VicKo ottis
LInda Ludwig
incatudwig
FEIMenb Vickie Ottis
Linda Ludwig
Linda ludwig
cindailaidwICs
W Beehive: n
BrarcloniBrnntl
BRandon Bronn
知Bw
BrandoniBrant
BramctoiBryaI
FLAw Hazeuaohansan
LIZIArChOT
NUta HazelUohansen
LIZ ArChOr
NEEUtOt HazelJohansen
品算
Liz Archer
MAtt Hazel Johansen
Lz Archer
Liz Archer
MichrilelHo
JA1m-9E
回/
Steve
∷∷∷∷∷
S
teve
:∷::
steve
Steve
∷
睚
r
C
气
C可
BCa
C
Cu
Ly
cy
C
T
F
C
r
C通
ADon
sponsor (v)
Our unilveosy sponsor
our untversity sponsors 5 exchange
students wto spend one year studying here
our umityeoslry sponsors 45 exchange
students who spend one year studying bier
A. Our university sponsors 45 exchange
AOur umlyeosny sponsors 45 @xchange
students wtro spand one year studying here
our umitversny sponsors 405
rs46@
recipien war studying lere.
recipient (n)
Trisha was lher schoraRs rst demale,
cocuplent of (hre cnywtde stance far armand
Ttlsha was her schools first demale
pQB60邮 ppup en go uoidr
可更同画圆
pgMe 4IE0 OUBS epAMP e0 o luolan
可更叫题圆
Trisha was her schools first Cemal
cOciplent (f (hre citywide scence lalr awand
0 esurient0wddo仙tad
Trisha was her schools健p
recipient of Chre clyde selene fatr awad
pB聊pud
Trisha was her schools (rsl female
recipient f the clyde sctenree far awand
pB apeg eames pptp emm a udpag
q画圆
Trisha was her schools ( rst female
trient of he cny/tde sclence Datr awand
0OsLpientof Ghre cnywtlle hanno fhr arnd
rO
△
C
S了
IuoTo
UOTo
o30
文胃
中团做
Oss
15SO中备动S
worldwid
器中英略sS(O
rowle
n文鲁阳
空中弟插做宿
n文㈤
产中固做
OSSO
Lidwina
n文x㈤
空中Z钩
OSSrOO
worldwid n
n文㈤
虢空中Z弦
Gss「OO
orld n
n文
月呲中舔
rowid n
I want to hel
p young peoplers
Worldwide
OO. 15S0D OLLI
4 PIMp
Croidoad sunon djay on ueM I
OOJSSD OILL
4 pINtO
rreidoad 6unok djay ou ueM I
I want to help young peopleg
worldwid n
lucio Clossroo
and a dream and you want tol
worldwid.
juicio Clossroo
Leadership Foundation (ILF
Worldwid n
Lucio Classroom
students for leadership training
Worldwid n
clio Cossor
governmental
agencies转
rOwid e
tulio Clossroo
governmental agencieS ER
worldwid D
lucio CIossroo
governmental agencies:
worldwid n
Clio ClossroO
governmental
agencies:
rowid n
hu7clio Cossroo
governmental
agencieS iaMR
rowid n
orlfwlc
Hucho classroo
Ico
CSSYOO
CISSroo
Q
Ho Classroo
(soo
(ission
ScOC
病CC
J))!
idoL
P
Rachel
中明
空中龉
空中做室
空中弟
中西
空中劳慰蜜
空中弟室
空中英吧弘安
空中弟吗
中
空中吗蜜
中英数
空中弟蜜
空中英
空中劳吗
空中弟吗
空中劳弘
空中弟
空中吗盟
空中劳
空中英只
空中弟
空中劳
中出安
中弟牧
空中劳品室
空中英弦至
空中妄
空中劳窑
空中英温妄
空中
空中弟函窟
空中装
望中英室
中
空中室
空中萌妄
空中第伍家
空中临室
空中弟弦宝
空中劳
空中弟
空中弟室
空中伍
空中弟涵室
空中劳伍室
空中弟
空中劳弦室
空中类品装妄
空中弟室
空中劳弦
空中弟色
空中英临
空中劳
空中弟窑
空中英
空中弟
空中弟蜜
中英安
空中英致
空中弟
空中英马
空中吧生室
空中劳蜜
空中吗
空中弟吗
空中劳慰室
空中弟蜜
空中英
史中弟临蜜
空中弟帖
空中劳弦室
空中弟蜜
空中端案
空中吗兴
空中英室
空中英
空中弟做窟
空中弟榴
中英
空中荣
空中弟蜜
空中劳吗室
空中劳蜜
空中弟蜜
空中劳数
空中弟室
空中慰
空中吗
空中劳室
增中币
空中弦室
空中e窟
空中弟弦室
空中英础做室
空中语蜜
空中室
空中劳c
空中美室
应中法热数害
空中美慰案
中热密
空中
空中美做室
中
空中数
空中法热c密
空中法热密
空中美宿
应中美慰密
空中美
空中英做室
空中美c室
应中劳室
空中害
空中英数
空中美慰室
中热c
空中美c室
空中续
空中美室
空中劳致密
空中美慰
空中劳数宝
空中美慰室
空中数
空中英
空中弟室
空中美
应中英话弦妄
女中室
空中弟
中话案
空中弟函案
空中软室
空中英
②中会
空中室
空中英函案
空中弟弦室
空中英函室
空中程
空中弟
空中劳吗
空中萌
空中弟吗蜜
冲英数
空中萌宰
空中弟吗蜜
空中劳
空中弟蜜
空中吗
空中英弦室
空中美慰座
空中英吗室
空中弟案
空中吗室
空中弟
空中英监
空中弟吗盗
空中弟
空中
中第
空中英
空中弟吗做
空中劳
空中荣中
空中弟
空中劳吗
空中
空中吗
空中弟窟
空中英宝
空中弟数窟
空中吗
空中弟蜜
空中
空中弟
空中弟狱室
空中
空中劳品室
空中英函弦
空中萌疯
空中英
空中萌品弦妄
空中弟品狱室
空中伍弦室
空中弟函
空中英伍弦室
空中弟做室
空中
空中弟室
空中英品妄
空中劳室
空中英品弦
空中
空中劳出妄
空中弟做
空中弦
空中英软窗
空中劳做室
空中英妄
空中弟函弦
空中英温骗室
空中弟室
空中英函弦家
空中骗
空中英品弦
空中弟
空中做窟
空中英
中伍
空中弟函室
空中做盒
空中室
空中弟吗蜜
空中
中英
空中弟
空中劳数
空中英只室
空中吗蜜
空中
会
空中吗
生中弟吗室
中劳吗做蜜
空中劳数
空中弟吗窟
空中英
空中劳室
空中英数客
空中密
应中法热
空中法c
中获热客
应中法热c
中均数密
应中意
空中数意
应中法热c密
应中热慰客
空中热数密
空中法致
应中法c
加中数
劳慰室
空中热致密
空中英数客
空中
应中法c意
应中美热密
空中热密
空中数
应中美热监密
空中荣
中监密
应中法功c
中英数密
应中法c密
应中英热做密
应中法c
中均数宝
空中热c密
应中美热密
应中法c害
应中美热
中热意
空中法致
空中英数密
空中
应中热密
空中热c室
空中线
空中法热c
空中英均数
空中美室
空中英数
空中均
空中劳慰室
空中
空中法热致室
空中荣数喜
空中英
中满监
空中满函构程
空中英监
空中益
空中骏左
空中弦窑
空中劳做
空中
空中信骑启
空中D
空中英伍弦
空中劳窟
空中劳弦
h始中
空中劳
空中英伍
空中函弦案
空中劳室
空中索
空中弟
空中英弦
空中劳室
在中美出做套
中弟室
空中
空中劳奖
空中弟
空中弟室
空中狗
空中烯室
空中装
空中英品室
空中弟窑
中弦室
空中类室
空中室
空中英品启
空中弟鱼
空中室
空中弟窟
空中英疯妄
空中劳品做室
空中弟函
空中英函弦
空中美室
空中英弦
空中弟
空中英只
空中弟牧
空中英
空中弟
空中英安
空中吗批
空中弟
空中类安
空中劳
空中弟超
空中吗
空中劳弦左
空中弟龉室
空中
空中第吗窟
空中英
空中第吗
空中
空中弟龉蜜
空中弟吗程
空中劳蜜
空中弟室
空中
空中弟吗窟
空中劳慰左
空中弟
突中劳室
空中劳慰
中萌
中英
中劳
空中荣
望中荣室
空中家
空中弟数
空中
空中弟出案
空中英
空中弟弦案
空中慰窟
中室
空中劳监窟
空中弟出做室
空中英监安
空中弟吗
空中劳热慰
空中吗
中中英
空中
空中劳室
中中
中英
空中劳吗
空中弟蜜
空中英
品钟中西
空中弟吗蜜
空中
中中宝
空中弟吗
空中
空中弟蜜
空中劳
空中弟吗
0&N
More INFO
More info
ore INFO
More INFO
More info
More nto
More INFO
lore INFO
More nto
More INFO
More nro
More Info
oreN下0
More INFO
More
N
下0
More info
More INrO
More nto
More INFO
ore
N
More info
ore
INFO
oreN下0
More Info
ore
N
More nro
ore
N
More Info
More nto
More
N
下0
More nro
U0
k
22人
SoRtor
sponsor
H
e
号
recipient
产
=
internship
ternship
H
Vicki
Ken
了=K@m
了Wek
re VhekieKen
ckl
Ken
等W0Km
她W=@m
》ese=-Km
VickieKen
F
public servant
等csem
civil servant
public sector
等pe
sni nate sat
private sector
ccic:re chinen
public sector
sni nite 381u
private-sector
civil service examination
appointed
u appointed
等pomd
appointed
Te appoint
appoint
named
pupu
civil service examination
c'll be rinit hack
Don'l go away.
Well be right back.
曰
n
Ni
:
C
产
C可
Bc
C
P
negotiation(n)
I nego
and manau
negotiation
The negotiation process between (he laborunion
SHes( Joy uo o Aemm puemmebeueu pue
uoUq用 eq sses@d uonelobou
he negotiation process between the labarunion
and management may go on for several weaks
congressman(n)
o CommIs
piano foun osman(n)
My father callad our loeal congressman
d00顶p甲moo
usso6uo卩pq
My father called our loeal congressman
C
ir
L
Shurry
Shuto Cinta
5x(
p
TOO
siNO
罐文
月
lOSSY
rwa
丹中购(ssO
riw
n文
中弟Z做室
文睛
空中钩
lOSSo
rowid
文睛
losso
worldwid n
n文睛㈤
诚空中弟Z
4 PILlO
emn
dwid n
Americans, "Young Ambassadors
orlilwld n
americans "Young ambassadofsHa
rowid D
tulio Classroom
a pIMplo
sQuv6uno人以Q
on public policy, businessmAN
Worldwid.
hu1clio Clossroo
government offices, and they ar
worldwid
COSSrOOI
government leaders. EA5AEAR
worldwid a
clio Clossroo
government leaders. BaeR
worldwid n
tulio Clossroo
government leaders.幽
orldIwld
tulio Clossroo
government leaders朋
worldwid
tulio Clos
enthusiasm and experience tod
worldwide
clio Cossroo